Okay, what up, y'all? We're back with a
brand new video. Make sure to like and
subscribe if you appreciate the content.
Today, we're covering, kind of
showcasing, the Krita model. Um, I'm
going to run these four reference images
through my pipeline, just kind of show
you what it can do with a consistent
character lower trained.
And, uh, that's going to be the video.
I'm not going to be doing the whole
training process in this video. Uh, this
will be on the school community. So, if
you want to learn how to train, link in
the description.
Uh, the reason why I do that, by the
way, is that I don't want to get banned
on YouTube again. Um, last time I got
banned was because I did something
similar to that.
So, I don't want to do it again. [__]
>> [snorts]
>> Now, let's run, uh, the pipeline. Um,
I'll explain how it works, but
essentially this model is one of the
best when it comes to AI for certain
[__]
Uh, it's not even really close, to be
honest. Uh, this model is absolutely
cracked. The the the the knowledge it
has,
uh, when it comes to everything is just
kind of crazy for its size.
Because I'm pretty sure you can run this
on like a 12 gigs VRAM GPU. Like, it's
really small, and it's really great. And
it only needs eight steps to get a good
image. So, really happy with the model
in general, and it does have control net
capabilities. So, you can kind of copy
the composition of other images pretty
easily using the control net, um, group
here.
In this video, I'm not going to do, um,
control net, okay? I'm just going to do
a straight prompting, uh, just so we can
see the actual capabilities of the
model. Uh, I just ran the first image
here, and this is what we got. So, if
you compare to this,
I mean,
I I mean, I think it looks pretty good.
Let me know in the comments what you
think. Um,
but I can I can say that, uh, the face
and the body of my character is pretty
consistent in this image. Um we can try
the second one here.
Boom. So, the pipeline essentially
what's happening is
uh you load images and you plug them
directly in my node. Uh I made this
node, but you can use whatever node you
want, really.
Um
you send the image to an LLM. The LLM
has a system prompt that it can it kind
of just follows what you ask it to
prompt. Uh so, you can put your uh the
features of your character directly in
there.
And then, uh it's going to create the
prompt, send it to the K sampler, and
uh you already know the rest, right? So,
[snorts] this is what we got for the
selfie. If you compare here,
I mean, the composition is definitely
different, but when it comes to image
quality and the the quality of the
actual costume, I think this one is
significantly better. And this is a real
image, right? So, we're comparing a real
image to an AI image, and the AI image,
I mean, it just has more details when it
comes to the costume and stuff. It's
just better.
Uh if we were to use the ControlNet, we
would get a similar composition. Let me
try it, actually. Let me just do it for
this one.
I'll just do it just kind of just so you
guys can see. Um
but yeah, model super great, and it's
fully uncensored, by the way. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's fully
uncensored. Uh you just need a couple of
things to, you know, get it going, but
once you get it going, it's really like
one of the best models.
So, here, as we can see with the
ControlNet, we get a similar
composition, and uh the body type of my
character is still conserved.
>> [music]
>> So, great model.
Um let's do uh the next one.
This one uh can be hard. This is an
unconventional position. Um and we're
not going to use a ControlNet not just
yet. We might just run it after. At this
point, why not? Already do it already
did one. Um I do have a hard 15-minute
limit on my videos on YouTube now.
Uh if you were following me before, I
was doing you know, full hour [music]
videos on my channel, but I just can't
do with it. I just can't [music] do that
anymore. So, unfortunate, but everything
is on the school. So, everything uh that
you might, you know, want to look at
will be on school. And this is a great
That's great.
>> [music]
>> And we don't even use the ControlNet
here.
Yeah, that's kind of crazy. I ain't
going to lie.
I'm not going to lie. That's pretty
good. Okay, that's that's insane. And if
we use a ControlNet, it's just going to
flip the image essentially because this
image is perfect.
Could use that for social media, I'm
pretty sure.
Obviously, we the the text here is, you
know, gibberish, but who gives a [__]
right?
So, we turned on uh the ControlNet and
what's the difference here?
There's
barely any difference in the image.
The image should be flipped.
So, it does have an issue with the
ControlNet. Oh, it's pretty low here.
Let me turn it to one.
Let's just try again with one. Maybe it
wasn't high enough.
But the fact that it also creates the
gameplay is pretty crazy because
usually it would just either put a black
screen or you know, some random [__]
on the screen. And uh this one actually
makes the game play.
Well, that's interesting. This is with
the ControlNet on,
right? So, positioning is one-to-one,
basically. And the text over over on the
top is also good, right? So,
uh really good performance here. Really
impressed with that. I hadn't tried it
before with this specific image, and I'm
pretty impressed here.
Uh let's do the last one. Uh that's
going to be a selfie with the feet up.
No ControlNet. Let's just see what it
does by itself, and then we're going to
run with the ControlNet. And that's
going to be the video.
Uh if you want to learn how to train
your Laura to get a consistent face and
body,
join the school, and um
you'll be able to kind of just follow
the tutorial over there.
Uh
and uh yeah. Let's see here.
Okay, so we did the selfie. We don't
quite get the feet fully in the shot.
Um I'm sure we could get the feet if we
really wanted to. We can just randomize
and run it again. Just Let's just try
that. Just going to see
um if it can do it or not.
And we see the feet here.
Um so, yeah. Um obviously, it can do it
pretty easily.
Yeah. And we have the right amount of
toes on every feet. So, that's pretty
good.
Uh we can run it with the ControlNet,
but at this point, it's basically the
same image. Um let's just do it, though.
>> [snorts]
>> Let's just see here
what we get. Okay, it's definitely the
composition did change. Uh the position
of the feet is clearly uh more um you
know
obvious.
But [music] there's an issue going on
over here. So
ControlNet's going to be hit or miss.
It just got trained. It could be better.
I'm not going to sit there and say it's
the best ControlNet ever.
But it does the job for most images and
you can just turn it down or up if you
need to.
So that's pretty much it for the
showcase of the model. If you want to
learn how to train this model, I'll
repeat it. Join the School community
and join the course. You'll be able
you'll have the whole thing over there.
And
I might I might release it on YouTube
later, but it's not going to be on
YouTube first, okay?
That's pretty much it. I hope you
enjoyed the video.
Great model
and yeah, I'll have the full
pipeline
on School as well. So if you want to try
this workflow without a without a Laura,
you can do that as well.
And that's going to be it. Shout out to
y'all and I'll see you in the next one.
Peace.